OUR STICKY LOVE
Did the association get
this year's donation?
They did, sir.
2026 NATIONAL SPORTS FESTIVAL
HIGH SCHOOL TEAM LINEUP
COACH: HONG DO-YEOP
ASSISTANT COACH: JANG TAE-HA
Hong Do-yeop.
Jang Tae-ha.
They're together?
So the man who despised anyone
who fought outside the ring
took back his precious disciple.
The pride of Gujin, Kim Pil-seung!
You've got this!
He's got this.
That's not what she should be doing
right about now.
Before I lost my memory,
maybe I was a pro…
A prodigy!
-You were amazing.
-You're smart.
She lost her memory?
We found her location.
It's said that she lives in Gujin
with Jang Tae-ha.
I need to see for myself.
Is this yours, sir?
Thank you.
No problem.
But
is that really yours?
It looks like a woman's watch.
Does it?
You have a keen eye.
It's clearly too small for your wrist.
It used to be a woman's…
but now it's mine.
Okay.
I'll see you again.
What's wrong with me?
It's not even cold, but I have the chills.
The thing is, I've never seen him
around the village before.
He was wearing
a really nice and expensive suit
and had a full head of hair
and these super intense eyes.
But what's weird is
he had a woman's watch.
-Do you know who he is?
-I sure do.
Who is he?
What do you think it means
when a man with intense eyes goes around
wearing a woman's watch?
It means he's lost his marbles.
You're here, Song-wol.
PAYCHECK
What's this? "Paycheck"?
Wait, I get paid?
Yay me!
It's cute, my paycheck.
Now that you got paid,
why not buy yourself some new clothes?
You like to dress up, don't you?
So,
you're saying that you're Baek Sang-gil,
Chairman of Mirae Eden.
But why did you come to see me?
If you don't mind me asking.
Why did you meet Gwak Chi-hyeon, Doctor?
Prosecutor Go… I mean, Go Ji-won
was an amnesia patient
who came to see me about a month ago.
She was suspicious
of her current boyfriend,
and one day, she said she remembered
a man named Gwak Chi-hyeon.
She wanted to know the truth,
so I tracked him down and met with him.
Then why did you tell Gwak Chi-hyeon
that you didn't know Prosecutor Go?
I was scared.
It seems as though
something big is going on,
and I'd rather not get involved.
I'm just a regular doctor
who runs a small clinic in the country.
I really don't know anything.
So I would be very grateful
if you could please leave now.
When do you think
Prosecutor Go will get her memory back?
That's impossible to know.
Aren't you her doctor?
I'm her doctor, yes. Not a fortune…
I'm sorry. That came out a bit…
There must be a way
to get her memory back quicker,
mustn't there?
Tae-ha.
Hands off.
You can kill me, sir.
You don't have to kill me nicely.
You can do whatever you want to me
until your anger is gone.
Please…
Please just spare Prosecutor Go's life.
She doesn't have her memory right now.
She doesn't even know
that she was a prosecutor.
She can't do you any harm, sir.
Tae-ha.
Yes?
Enough with the melodrama.
Why did you let her live?
She's someone I owed from a long time ago.
The Jang Tae-ha, who worked like a machine
for 14 years without a single slipup,
did all this because of
some petty sentiment?
Come with me.
Say hi to your boys. It's been a while.
Had they served you well,
you never would have made
the wrong choice.
Such a shame.
No!
Sir!
Jang Tae-ha, don't move!
The boys are to blame for that.
Please stop!
Sir!
Hurt me instead!
Come on, that's not right.
You know how fond I was of you.
I'd never do something
this childish to you.
Sir!
No, don't!
Tae-ha, sir!
Sir!
Tae-ha!
Throughout both Eastern
and Western history,
people didn't use guns or knives
to torture the worst of them.
Instead, they covered their eyes
with a single black cloth.
The fear of not knowing what will happen
is scarier than any gun or knife.
I know what you're planning.
Go on and try.
But every day, your imagination will
eat away at you, wondering about my plan…
for you…
and Prosecutor Go.
Escort Director Jang home,
respectfully.
Jang Tae-ha seems unaware of the extra
evidence Gwak Chi-hyeon mentioned.
If he had it, he wouldn't have begged.
He would have tried to negotiate.
Only Prosecutor Go knows
where that evidence is.
But she can't remember.
If we just take care of her now--
No. That bitch, Prosecutor Go,
must have had a plan B.
If it's buried somewhere
and manages to surface somehow,
it'll be the end for me and Mayor Ju.
We must find and destroy it.
In order to do that…
we have to stir Prosecutor Go's memory.
Hey, Tae-ha.
Tae-ha, what did you mean by that?
Baek Sang-gil was here?
Did you meet him?
Is Eun-sae okay?
I have to go somewhere now.
I'll tell you the details when I get back.
Please protect Eun-sae while I'm gone.
-Okay.
-Of course.
Goodness.
Jang Tae-ha.
Gi-jun, I need your help.
No, I don't want to. I won't.
I really don't want to be involved
in this anymore.
Go Eun-sae has amnesia.
Now's the best time to deal with her
before her memory returns.
And yet, Baek Sang-gil kept her alive.
Why do you think that is?
How would I know?
I'm asking because I have a hunch.
You meeting Gwak Chi-hyeon.
What about that?
I made sure Gwak Chi-hyeon
couldn't make a move.
But he was wandering around,
searching for Go Eun-sae.
That means Baek Sang-gil
still has a use for him.
He must need something more
from Go Eun-sae.
We need to find out what that is.
Gi-jun, please.
You're my only hope.
I really don't want to. You…
We're not close, so you must not know,
but I'm a huge scaredy-cat.
I can't watch Unanswered Questions.
It freaks me out.
What's that show called?
Surprise Mystery TV: Truth or Fiction?
I can't watch it
because it makes my heart race.
Gi-jun, please help me.
I said I won't--
What…
Su-ji.
I left something behind.
This day's driving me crazy.
What does Jang Tae-ha want you
to help him with?
What?
Okay, fine.
Let's hear what it is
you want me to help you with.
What is it?
CHEONAN SAMGEORI REST STOP
What did he say? Did you find out?
When do you think
Prosecutor Go will get her memory back?
Why would Chairman Baek Sang-gil…
Why would he come to you…
To be honest,
I prefer to stay out of messy affairs,
so I played dumb.
But since the chairman himself
came all the way
to ask me about Go Ji-won,
I think it's time I knew
what's going down.
What does Chairman Baek want
from Prosecutor Go?
Why would I tell you that?
How could I trust you?
I made sure Gwak Chi-hyeon
couldn't make a move.
I heard you almost died.
Please, no!
No!
Wait. How do you even know about that?
Chairman Baek told me.
I'm sure you know very well
that for people like us,
the moment we are rendered useless,
we're done.
But now that the chairman
has actually found Go Ji-won,
we need to be of help to him in some way
in order for us both to live.
Don't you think?
Let's find it together.
How we can be of help.
What is it
that the chairman wants
from Prosecutor Go?
Chairman Baek Sang-gil
and Mayor Ju Min-jong.
There's another piece of evidence
linking them.
Never make me do this again.
It was no easy feat, you know.
He's not exactly the talkative type.
But since I'm a psychiatrist
and I understand human psychology,
I have a way with words.
You should know
that I got him to talk on pure skill.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, I'm not done.
Would it be okay
if I heard you out another time?
No, it's not that.
This.
I bought this on my way to Seoul.
It's the latest model
that detects all wiretaps and GPS devices.
What if Baek Sang-gil planted something
while watching you?
I also bought one and checked,
but there was nothing, at least in my car.
And still, I'm whispering like this.
You always have to be vigilant.
Thanks, Gi-jun.
I'll make sure to repay you for your help.
Don't mention it.
Guess I'm pretty damn cool too.
What? Information
about the stowaway boat plan leaked?
It seems so. I lost contact
with one of the Japanese brokers.
I know what you're planning.
Go on and try.
Can we arrange another date?
Not unless we want a serious delay.
Can you at least change the time
the boat leaves that day?
I'm relying on you, Kaito.
Just like in Namba, Osaka, ten years ago.
There's nothing in our gym.
Baek Sang-gil never leaves loose ends.
Now that he knows there's more evidence,
he won't kill Go Eun-sae
until he finds and destroys it.
In a way, it's lucky she lost her memory.
The best move is to smuggle her out
as soon as possible.
We need to send Go Eun-sae away
this Thursday, no matter what.
And you?
Will you be okay?
Yes.
Baek Sang-gil will think
there's a chance I have the evidence,
so he won't do anything rash.
I'll be going now.
Okay.
Go on.
What do we do?
Will Tae-ha really be okay?
He's not a fool.
I'm sure he's already got a plan
in that head of his.
How will he ever send Eun-sae away?
And how will Eun-sae go on without Tae-ha?
Yeah, it's not like people can control
how they feel.
How do you break a bond
that's grown so deep?
Here!
My paycheck got this.
It was my first paycheck
after losing my memory.
And I was thinking, "What should I buy?"
People say, if nothing else,
that good shoes are a must.
You should have treated yourself.
I already have everything I want.
No matter how much I think about it,
all I need is Jang Tae-ha.
What's with that face?
Is it because of that superstition
that if you give someone shoes,
they'll run away?
I gave them to you
with a different meaning.
From now on, let's walk together.
So, from now on,
no need to try so hard on your own.
Let's do everything together.
Speaking of which…
Put it towards your grandma's meds.
Go Eun-sae.
You're touched.
Well, I guess
I just like Jang Tae-ha that much.
From now on, let's walk together.
I looked into what you asked me to.
It's possible.
Good work.
And I just transferred some money
to your account.
Send it to the guys who got hurt today.
-Sir, you don't have to--
-They got hurt because of me.
How did you survive that world
with such a soft heart?
And how will you ever send her away?
She didn't even buy
the clothes she wanted today
so she could buy you a present.
You like each other so much.
How will you two live
after you send her away?
Speaking of which…
I'm going to need everyone's help.
Are you going somewhere today?
To work.
What work?
Surely, you're not going
to the gym like that?
Jang Tae-ha, wait.
This isn't right.
You're really going to go back
to that life?
I found a hospital
specializing in geriatric cancer care.
For Grandma's surgery.
I can't afford the hospital bills
with my salary from the gym.
Still, this is wrong.
How can you go back to being a gangster?
Then do you have a better idea?
I'll find a way to make money with you.
-Take every job I can--
-You're unidentified.
-Isn't that Tae-ha?
-It's Tae-ha and Eun-sae.
Tae…
What's going on? Something seems off.
Jang Tae-ha!
-I think they had a fight.
-Is she crying?
Ladies.
What are you doing?
Nothing at all.
Something's going on with them, right?
Something out of the ordinary, right?
Talk.
We've all got several decades
under our belts.
You think we can't read a room? Tell us!
We've been sensing something
for a few days now.
Strangers have been
creeping into our quiet village.
And on roads only ever used
by a few tractors,
we saw a huge, black Mercedes-Benz.
Tell us.
What on earth is going on?
-Tell us.
-Talk.
-Talk!
-Tell us.
Tell us.
A prosecutor from Seoul?
Then this whole thing
was an act to save our Eun-sae,
who has no memory?
I'm telling you this knowing
that Tae-ha will beat me to death.
Because I think we could also use help
from you S.E.S ladies.
-Okay.
-Goodness.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
Please help me, Mr. Hong.
Jang Tae-ha listens to you.
So please persuade him. Please?
It's no use.
Mr. Hong has already tried everything
to stop him.
But you know he's as stubborn as a mule.
That darned punk.
What now?
You despise gangsters, Eun-sae.
I can't believe it.
He promised me
that he would never use violence again.
He's not one to break promises.
How could Jang Tae-ha…
Hey, so you're really…
Can you prepare a two-month supply
of medicine for her?
And something to calm her
when she's feeling down.
Do you think doing this will change
how she feels about you?
Go Eun-sae hates gangsters.
Maybe hating me
will make it hurt a little less.
That crazy bastard!
This is why I was so against
Pil-seung boxing.
If all you know is how to fight,
it's easy to go down that path.
That's what I'm saying.
I thought that punk
had gotten his act together.
But back to being a thug?
He's a lost cause, he is.
Looking back now,
it's a huge relief
you didn't walk down the aisle.
Eun-sae.
That jerk, Tae-ha. Just dump him already!
I should get home.
Tae-ha.
There must be a way.
Maybe there's nothing we can do right now,
but one day,
I'm sure there will be a way.
I know saving lives is the priority,
but you shouldn't get hurt.
You can't underestimate the power of food.
You need a full belly to do great things.
All this while, every day,
every moment must have felt like
walking a tightrope
with that enormous burden.
Thank you.
As of now, we have no choice
but to send Eun-sae away
if we want to save her, right?
Yes.
And is there anything we can do to help?
Are you okay?
I was so startled.
Even so, how could you collapse like that?
You need to learn to protect yourself.
Easy for someone like you to say.
Want me to teach you?
First, get into this position.
If someone attacks you head-on,
you just need to turn your body like this.
Just by turning away,
you can avoid a fatal injury.
Let's try it.
-That's it.
-Like this?
And if someone attacks you from behind…
Try grabbing me from behind.
Like this?
Then…
Step on their foot,
elbow them in the stomach,
stick your leg out to trip them up…
and run away.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
When someone attacks me from behind,
I step on their foot,
elbow them in the stomach,
stick my leg out to make them fall,
and run away.
You're good.
That's cool. It really works.
Let me try one more time.
Okay.
And then…
Step on their foot…
It's a little hard to move if you do this.
Jang Tae-ha.
Go Eun-sae.
Don't take it too hard.
If you just keep living…
everything passes.
You just need to stay alive.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry for startling you.
For hurting you.
The wind's cold.
I'll get you a jacket.
THE DAY OF THE ESCAPE
-Looks delicious.
-Right, well…
No particular reason.
You just seemed so down because of Tae-ha,
so, to cheer you up,
I thought we'd all get together
and share a meal.
-Yeah.
It's the tofu poke that you like.
I made the tofu myself.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Everyone.
Let's eat, okay?
You know,
I didn't see the tag
and accidentally bought a size small.
Pity.
Why don't you just wear it, Eun-sae?
But this is…
And this…
I made this
when I still had my spiritual powers.
Carry it with you. It'll be effective.
-Okay.
-That's precious.
Here!
This is lion's mane liquor.
Take it.
But this is…
Isn't this your most prized possession?
You can find mushrooms everywhere
if you dig with a hoe.
I can just make more.
But…
This much?
Song-wol.
What is all this, everyone?
Are you all giving me gifts
to cheer me up?
TAFFY VILLAGE PHOTO CONTEST
-This is us making taffy.
-Right?
Yes, it is.
-Look at this.
-Do you want a picture?
At the karaoke bar.
How pretty.
That's a good one.
You look like an actress.
This is you guys.
What's wrong? We look great.
You and Song-wol look great in this one.
-How lovely.
-You look so pretty.
I really love this village.
The scenery is beautiful,
and I love the sweet smell
of boiling taffy.
Of course.
Right?
Being born and raised in Taffy Village,
I learned that relationships
are like sweet taffy.
Once you form a bond,
it's not easy to break it.
That's right.
And the warmer it gets,
the more it sticks.
Even if you want to spit it out halfway,
it gets so stuck that you can't.
That's why
if it's meant to be, it'll stick.
You're bound to meet again.
When you think about it,
saying that something is like taffy
is a good thing.
I wonder how it came to be used
in a bad way.
Tae-ha.
You're here. Come.
Hey.
We have to go.
Where?
I'll tell you on the way.
Go on.
Everyone, choose your photos
and don't forget to save me some.
-Sure.
-We'll be back.
-All right.
-Okay.
See you tomorrow.
And we were just starting to get attached.
Oh dear.
We're going for fresh air?
It's been tough lately.
You could use a change of scenery.
You should get changed.
We're going to see the ocean,
so dress warmly.
DAEDANG PORT
I think this is the first time
I've been this far from Taffy Village.
We've seen the sea together before,
haven't we?
Yes.
Is something wrong?
You haven't looked so good for a while.
If you're tired, we can turn back.
It's fine.
What's wrong? What's going on?
What's going on?
Listen carefully.
Don't come out no matter what,
and follow Gang-rok when he gets here.
What? To where?
Jang Tae-ha.
Where are you…
Get him!
Jang Tae-ha!
Open it!
Get on, now! We don't have time!
-Tae-ha.
-Go, now!
We need to hurry!
Now!
He'll be right behind us.
Hey, stop them!
What's going on?
Hurry up and explain.
He's trying to save you.
You're going to Japan now.
What on earth are you talking about?
Just go and stay there for now.
That's the only way for you to live.
What about Jang Tae-ha?
Is he coming too?
Yes.
Eun-sae.
Jang Tae-ha's really coming, right?
Of course.
If you just wait in there for a bit,
he'll be here in no time.
Okay.
Gang-rok.
Jang Tae-ha…
I'm Tae-ha's friend, Kaito.
I'll escort you from here.
-Please follow me.
-You can follow him.
He's Tae-ha's man.
I'll go to Tae-ha. Kaito.
This way.
We leave in ten minutes.
Sorry?
Then what about Jang Tae-ha?
KAITO
BOARDING COMPLETE
TIMER
No. I don't want to go.
Where would I go without Jang Tae-ha?
Where is Jang Tae-ha? He was badly hurt.
Jang Tae-ha is risking his life
to save you.
Don't mess this up.
How does blood taste after so long?
Jang Tae-ha is Jang Tae-ha after all.
You managed to save Prosecutor Go.
But did you really think
that boat wouldn't have…
my men on it?
I was just playing with you.
A bit of nostalgia.
And I got to see you fight
like your life was on the line.
Can you at least change the time
the boat leaves?
I'm relying on you, Kaito.
Just like in Namba, Osaka, ten years ago.
Is someone listening in?
I think so. I'm thinking of getting a boat
with a modified motor.
That's too risky.
If we go too fast,
the Coast Guard will spot us.
We have to take the risk.
I'll get the boat ready.
And I can distract the Coast Guard.
I looked into what you asked me to.
It's possible.
This boat leaves in three minutes.
We don't have time.
We need to transfer quickly.
TRANSFERRED TO MOTORBOAT
DEPARTING
Chairman, sir.
Prosecutor Go isn't on the cargo ship.
What's happening…
No! Jang Tae-ha!
No!
I'm Prosecutor Go Ji-won.
We meet again, Prosecutor.
OUR STICKY LOVE
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi